<ElementDescriptions>
    <Element>
        <name>Term</name>
        <description>Name of the metadata element</description>
    </Element>
    <Element>
        <name>Definition</name>
        <description>Definition of the element</description>
    </Element>
    <Element>
        <name>entry</name>
        <description>Data type (free text or controlled vocabulary)</description>
    </Element>
    <Element>
        <name>DC equivalent</name>
        <description>Equivalent of the term in Dublin Core metadata elements</description>
    </Element>
    <Element>
        <name>Repeatable</name>
        <description>Whether the same term can be used in multiple terms (Yes or No)</description>
    </Element>
    <Element>
        <name>Modality</name>
        <description>Degree of necessity (Mandatory, Optional, Strongly Suggested, Mandatory if)</description>
    </Element>
    <Element>
        <name>Guideline</name>
        <description>Explanation of how to use</description>
    </Element>
    <Element>
        <name>An example data</name>
        <description>An example data</description>
    </Element>
</ElementDescriptions>

<Metadata>

    <term>Project ID</term>
    <definition>An alphanumeric identifier for the record created for the IF Repository.</definition>
    <entry>String-Free text</entry>
    <dcequilavent>dc:identifier</dcequilavent>
    <repeatable>No</repeatable>
    <modality>Mandatory</modality>
    <guideline>Unique project identifier given by IF repository.</guideline>
    <example>UFC0030</example>

    <term>Project Title</term>
    <definition>The name given to the project by the Project Leader in any language. </definition>
    <entry>String-Free text</entry>
    <dcequilavent>dc:title</dcequilavent>
    <repeatable>No</repeatable>
    <modality>Mandatory</modality>
    <guideline>Enter the whole title of the project you are involved in, including any subtitle. Do
        not use any punctuation between the title and subtitle. Only capitalize the first alphabet
        of the project title, acronyms and any personal and geographic names. </guideline>
    <example>In Search of LA</example>

    <term>Project Type</term>
    <definition>The name of the Imagining Futures Project Type.</definition>
    <entry>String-CV (Project types)</entry>
    <dcequilavent>dc:type</dcequilavent>
    <repeatable>Yes</repeatable>
    <modality>Optional</modality>
    <guideline>Provide the IF project type information. Choose between from the list.</guideline>
    <example>Start Up Projects (2020-2021)</example>

    <term>Project Region</term>
    <definition>The name of the Imagining Futures Project Regions.</definition>
    <entry>String-CV (Project regions)</entry>
    <dcequilavent></dcequilavent>
    <repeatable>Yes</repeatable>
    <modality>Optional</modality>
    <guideline>Provide the IF project region information. Choose between from the list.</guideline>
    <example>North America</example>

    <term>Related Project</term>
    <definition>The name of the related project.</definition>
    <entry>String-CV (Projects)</entry>
    <dcequilavent>dc:relation</dcequilavent>
    <repeatable>Yes</repeatable>
    <modality>Optional</modality>
    <guideline>Provide the name of the related project to this project. It could be Top Up or
        Starter project.</guideline>
    <example>History in the Streets</example>

    <term>Project Description</term>
    <definition>A textual description of the project including the aim and objectives, methods,
        scope and expected impacts.</definition>
    <entry>String-Free text</entry>
    <dcequilavent>dc:description</dcequilavent>
    <repeatable>No</repeatable>
    <modality>Mandatory</modality>
    <guideline>Provide textual description of the project in primary language limited to maximum of
        250 words. Include background information, aim, objectives, methods and impacts of the
        project.</guideline>
    <example>In Search of LA is a digital hub for documenting histories and telling stories about
        Los Angeles neighborhoods, past and present. It identifies and brings together resources
        from across the city, including local, community-based collections, digital archives, and
        institutional repositories, facilitating place-based research. In Search of LA enables
        collaborative history-making and demystifies the research process. It serves multiple
        audiences and supports community-based learning at UCLA, scholarly research, and public
        participation in the creation of historical narratives.</example>

    <term>Project Description Alt</term>
    <definition>A textual description of the project including the aim and objectives, methods,
        scope and expected impacts in another language or with different words.</definition>
    <entry>String-Free text</entry>
    <dcequilavent>dc:description</dcequilavent>
    <repeatable>No</repeatable>
    <modality>Optional</modality>
    <guideline>Provide a textual description of the project in an alternative language or using
        different words. The description should be limited to a maximum of 250 words and should
        include background information, the project's aim, objectives, methods, and its anticipated
        impacts.</guideline>
    <example></example>

    <term>Project Leader</term>
    <definition>The name of the Lead project investigator.</definition>
    <entry>String-CV (Participants)</entry>
    <dcequilavent>dc:rightsHolder</dcequilavent>
    <repeatable>Yes</repeatable>
    <modality>Mandatory</modality>
    <guideline>Provide the first name and last name (surname) of the lead project investigator.</guideline>
    <example>Tawny Paul</example>

    <term>Project Country</term>
    <definition>The name of the country where the project was carried out.</definition>
    <entry>String-CV (Country)</entry>
    <dcequilavent>dc:coverage</dcequilavent>
    <repeatable>Yes</repeatable>
    <modality>Optional</modality>
    <guideline>Provide the name of the country where the project was carried out.</guideline>
    <example>United States of America</example>

    <term>IF Webpage</term>
    <definition>A link to the project's Imagining Futures website.</definition>
    <entry>String-Free text</entry>
    <dcequilavent>dc:source</dcequilavent>
    <repeatable>No</repeatable>
    <modality>Optional</modality>
    <guideline>Provide the URL of the project's IF webpage.</guideline>
    <example>https://imaginingfutures.world/projects/in-search-of-la/</example>

    <term>External Website</term>
    <definition>A link to the project's alternative website.</definition>
    <entry>String-Free text</entry>
    <dcequilavent>dc:source</dcequilavent>
    <repeatable>No</repeatable>
    <modality>Optional</modality>
    <guideline>Provide the URL of the project'ss external webpage.</guideline>
    <example></example>
    
</Metadata>